Hello, hello friends, how are you all?
Welcome to your own YouTube channel Stock
Market Point. Friends, today we are going to talk
about ICICI Lombard and
what kind of moment it can try to show us in the coming time. So,
friends, before the start of the video, let me
tell you that I have decided some labels
for this. If we route the poor line of those levels,
we can see, then
we can see positive or negative moment.
Friends,
before the start of the video, a little information about this
YouTube channel for all of you.
All the money earned from this YouTube channel will be
given as a contribution for cow service.
Friends, so
definitely give your love and support to this YouTube channel. Along with this, you
must make your important contribution by watching this video completely. So friends, let's
start the video. So,
friends, let's talk about
what kind of moment we got to see today for ICICI Lombard. As
you all might be able to
see,
we got to see the negative moment of the rupee today.
And
if we talk about today's opening, then
Today we got its opening of Rs.1345
and if we talk about the same, friends, if we talk about
its closing yesterday, then
it gave us its closing yesterday around Rs.1401,
friends, so
friends, if we look at the opening and closing, then
we clearly get to see negative momentum in
it and
if we talk about its high, then the
quantity which touched Rs.1350 only
and the same negative moment of up to Rs.1350 has been
seen in it today, friends, let us
see that in the end, if
we look at its one month, sorry friends, if
we look at its one year moment, then
how has its one year movement been, then
exactly 365 days ago, friends, we
found it trading, you can see
that till around Rs.1372 and after that, the
positive movement it has shown is almost up to
Rs.1678,
friends, and after that, the
phase of decline which started in it, almost the
negative Mendis that we have seen is
negative till around Rs.1193
Friends, the moments showed that the price
struggled around these levels for a long time and when
we saw their breakout inside it, then
after that, till now it had shown a
positive moment, it has shown a positive moment up to Rs. 1412, so let's
talk friends,
after whose breakout we can
see a positive or negative moment inside it, before that friends, the
video is only for educational purposes, for
buying or selling,
definitely consult your advisor, so friends, if
you are still on this YouTube video, then
please like the video and subscribe to the channel and press the
notification bell
so that you keep getting such videos related to the market, so
friends, you can see that
we have two
support levels of this,
friends, the first support level is where it has
created its low today,
around Rs. 1316, if this level is
seen breaking out, then the second target of the
negative moment that we can see can be
1306,
friends, and let's talk about that, friends, if this
level  It also appears to be getting pregnant,
after that we see levels,
that is the area from 1228 to 1275 rupees,
friends, where it can create its support
level or the
decline which has started inside it at 12 and now,
it can stop, now let's talk
friends, for our positive side, we
need its moment on the positive side, so
how can we get its signals, so
friends, as we should have got the signal today
for its positive moment, at least the closing we needed was
around 1332 rupees, we
needed its closing, friends, so when it
gave us a closing on the up side from 1330 rupees, this level which it has created of 1347 rupees, has been
its support
level for a long time, if
we see this level breaking out, then again the
positive moments that we
can see, we can see positive moments from 1364 to 1375 above in
it,
friends, if you like the video  If you liked it,
please like this video and subscribe to the channel to get
notifications
so that you keep getting such videos related to the market. The
video is only for educational
purposes.
Do take advice from your advisor for buying and selling. So, see you
friends in the next video. Jai Hind.